[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "You must feel lucky to be alive, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Yes, sir, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "What are the injuries that you suffered?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Doctors said I had a cracked humerus in my shoulder, like a fracture.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "How were you feeling at that moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Honestly, sir, I believe very strongly that if it's your time to go, it's your time to go, and there's nothing you can do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "When these pictures emerged of the truck being thrown in the air, did your family know that was you, Jeremiah?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "IN", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Actually, I've been told pretty much all my family and all my friends saw it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeremiah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "I mean, did you see devastation around you, Jeremiah?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "I saw the debris in front of me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeremiah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "Jeremiah, when you -- when you look at the video pictures of that tornado hitting your truck, can you quite believe what you're watching?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Actually, the first time I saw it, after they took me to the hospital, I was laying in the hospital bed, and I was flipping through the channels because everybody was saying it was on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Do we know anything about who they are or what the likelihood that they survived?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "WP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Well, here's what we know, that they have confirmed 125 fatalities.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Is he at the hospital?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "He's either at the hospital -- I believe he's still out with the search.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "ORGAN: Do you believe this was a direct hit from the tornado on the home that's caused all this while Hank was out of town, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "Yes, definitely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hank"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VBN", ",", "VBN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Pam, how are the family coping with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "As you would expect, devastated, shocked, numb.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Were they all completely decimated?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Several homes were destroyed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Catherine", "Kathleen"]}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "RP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Do you know right now what the condition is of Catherine and Kathleen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "I believe they're both in stable condition right now and Catherine is either in surgery or just gotten out, and Kathleen is in stable condition.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Catherine", "Kathleen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Cunningham Park"]}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Where exactly are you right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Right now, I'm at the Cunningham Park.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Are they safe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Yes, unfortunately, we did lose all our materialistic items.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Is that your understanding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "What do you make of what you said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "What is it -- if you were to try to crystallize the magic of what Oprah's achieved with this show, what would you say it is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "POS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "I would say, without question, it's connection.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Oprah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Celine Dion"]}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Who do you think of all the celebrities in the world is the one that's appeared on the Oprah show the most?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "Celine Dion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Of all the great moments in the history of this show, which one for you was the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Oh, gosh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "My favorite moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Gayle, if you were to try to assess the impact that Oprah's show has had on America, what would you say it's been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "You know, there's not a day that's gone by that somebody doesn't come up to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Oprah"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "What did you feel when you heard her say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "You know, I just felt that she's really summing up how I feel.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Anderson, just before we leave you, this 1,500 people missing -- is there an expectation that the death toll is likely to rise pretty substantially from the current 126?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "There's no way to know sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "VBG", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "Would you know the answer to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "A very convincing answer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "POS", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "What is she like to work for in reality?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "It's interesting that's one of your favorite shows, one of your guilty pleasures.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "And in terms of how you chose the stories, who was the driving force, you or Oprah?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "VBG", "NN", ",", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "I pitched stories.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "What I always felt with Oprah -- the power of the Oprah brand came through her searing honesty, whether it was producing a great big trolley load of fat to show how much weight she had put on and lost and so on, or talking about her struggles with eating disorders, or whatever it may be, the abuse and so on -- it was the searing honesty, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "It was the searing honesty.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Oprah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Lisa, finally, what would you say is the big lesson you learned from Oprah?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "Well, first of all, she's one of the hardest working people I've ever met.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oprah"]}}]